(Sheldon:)and not the much more
ominous "hello."
(Penny:)What's going on?
(Sheldon:)I'm mad at Amy.
(Penny:)Did she leave pit stains
in your favorite crop top, too?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)She helped Barry Kripke make
an advancement in string theory.
(Penny:)Oh, that sounds
like a good thing.
(Sheldon:)Well, it would be,
except that I left string theory
(Sheldon:)because I decided
it was a dead end.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, and then she went
behind my back
(Sheldon:)to help someone else
prove me wrong.
(Sheldon:)My rival, no less.
(grunts)
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry you had to see that.
(Penny:)I'm sorry I didn't have
a camera.
(Sheldon:)Why would she
do this to me?
(Penny:)Well, I'm sure she didn't
upset you on purpose.
(Penny:)Besides, aren't you
the one who says
(Penny:)there's nothing more important
than the advancement of science?
(Sheldon:)No, I said there's
nothing more important
than me advancing science.
(Penny:)All right, well, if I'm
understanding this right,